As long as people are involved in modern-day crimes,
طالما جرائم العصر الحديث تتضمّن بشراً
there are no unsolvable mysteries!
!لا توجد ألغاز لا تُحلّ
Today's case is about a mysterious murder weapon!
!قضيّة اليوم عن سلاح جريمة غامض
Let's use our heads to figure it out!
!لنستعمل عقولنا ونكتشفه
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ دماغه لبالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
The Case of the Mysterious Murder Weapon
قضيّة سلاح جريمة القتل الغامض
It's nice to take a leisurely walk together once in a while!
من الجميل أنّ نتنزه نحن الثلاثة براحةٍ هكذا بين الحين والآخر
Yeah!
!أجل
What's so fun about walking with that runt?!
ما المسلّي في التنزه مع هذا القزم؟
What's wrong, Conan-kun?
ما الخطب يا كونان-كن؟
What is it, Conan-kun?
ما هذا يا كونان-كن؟
A little bird...
...طير صغير
Is it dead?
أهو ميت؟
No. It looks okay.
كلا، يبدو بخير
It's still alive.
لا يزال حيّاً
It doesn't seem to be hurt...
لا يبدو مُصاباً
It flew off...
...طار
What a weird bird. Maybe it had an anemic attack?
يا للطير الغريب، ربما كانت نوبة فقر دم
It's coming from that apartment building!
!إنّها من مجمع الشقق ذاك
Whoops...
...من أين
There are only two apartments occupied here!
توجد شقّتان مسكونتان فحسب
Can I help you?
كيف أساعدكم؟
We just heard a woman scream from this building!
!سمعنا صرخة مرأة من المبنى قبل قليل
Are you sure? I didn't hear anything...
...أأنت متأكد؟ لم أسمع شيئاً
Welcome back. You're back early.
مرحباً، رجعت باكراً
Is something the matter?
أهناك خطب ما؟
Well, these folks here--
...حسناً، هؤلاء الأشخاص يقولون
Are you all right?!
أأنتِ بخير؟
It's horrible! My husband!
!إنّها مصيبة! زوجي
My husband was murdered on our veranda!
!قُتل زوجي في شرفتنا
I'm Detective Mori.
أنا المتحرّي موري
I take it you're the one who screamed?
من أطلقت تلك الصرخة كانت أنت، صحيح؟
Which room is yours?
ما رقم شقّتكم؟
Room 715.
رقم 715
Say, I looked at the mail board earlier.
أخبرني، نظرتُ لصناديق البريد قبل قليل
Hardly anybody lives here, huh?
يكاد لا يعيش أحد هنا، صحيح؟
This place is going to be demolished this month.
سيُهدم هذا المبنى في هذا الشهر
So the only ones living here now
لذا المقيمون الوحيدون هنا
are Imoto, who runs his own business, and Terasawa-san here.
هما إيموتو الذي يدير عقاراته الخاصة، وتيراساوا-سان هذا
Allow me.
اسمح لي
High heels and two pairs of men's shoes...
زوج حذاء كعب عالٍ وزوجا أحذية رجال
Real Estate Agent Ryusuke Imoto, 39 years old
(ريوسكي إيموتو (39 رئيس وكالة عقارات
He's been hit in the back of the head.
ضُرب على مؤخرة رأسه
The murder weapon appears to have been a flower pot or the like.
يبدو أنّ سلاح الجريمة كان أصيص أزهار
Who are you?
من أنت؟
My name is Dobashi.
ا-اسمي دوباشي
Did you kill him?!
!أقتلته؟
No!
!كـ-كلا
So the cause of death was brain damage...
كان سبب الموت ضرراً دماغياً إذاً
The killer most likely lifted up a flower pot from behind him
رفع القاتل أصيص أزهار وراء الضحيّة غالباً
and brought it down as hard as possible.
وضربه بأقصى قوّته
Hey, Inspector.
حضرة المفتّش
There's a mark here,
يوجد أثر هنا
maybe it has something to do with the murder--
...ربما له علاقة بالجريمة
Alright, you!
!أنت
Will you ever learn to stop butting in during our investigations?!
!كفّ عن التدخل في التحقيق دوماً
Interesting.
صحيح
There definitely is a mark here.
يوجد أثر هنا بالفعل
It seems extremely new compared to all the other marks.
يبدو حديثاً مقارنة ببقيّة الآثار
The victim was Mr. Ryusuke Imoto, 39 years old
كان الضحيّة السيّد ريوسكي، 39 عاماً
and president of NEED, a real estate agency.
رئيس "نييد"، وكالة عقارات
It was his wife, Takako-san, who found him. Correct?
،من وجد الجثة كانت زوجته أنت يا تاكاكو-سان، صحيح؟
Yes.
أجل
And the person found standing in front of the body
والشخص الذي كان بجوار الجثّة
when Mori-kun and the others came rushing in...
...عندما وصل موري-كن والبقيّة مسرعين
My name is Dobashi. I manage an import company.
أُدعى دوباشي، أدير شركة استيراد
I'm Imoto-kun's former boss and the one who introduced him to his wife.
أنا مدير إيموتو-كن السابق ومن عرّفه على زوجته
I came to see him today about a business matter.
أتيتُ اليوم لرؤيته بشأن موضوع متعلّق بالعمل
His matchmaker, eh...
...وسيط العلاقة إذاً
And you are?
ومن تكون أنت؟
Terasawa. I live on the 5th floor of this building.
تيراساوا، أعيش في الطابق الخامس من هذا المبنى
I used to run a fishing goods store.
كنتُ أدير متجر معدّات صيد سمك
"Used to"?
كنت؟
Imoto took control of my store!
!استولى إيموتو على متجري
He used some dirty legal loophole to do it!
!استعمل ثغرةً قانونية دنيئة لفعل ذلك
He was a terrible man!
!كان رجلاً شنيعاً
My guess is he did the same sort of things to these people too!
قام بأشياء مشابهة لهذين الاثنين غالباً أيضاً
Well, you two?
ما قولكما؟
Yes.
حسناً
As their matchmaker, I shouldn't be saying this,
يُفترض ألّا أقول هذا بما أنّي وسيط علاقتهما
but he and his wife were in the middle of getting divorced
لكن كان إيموتو-كن وزوجته في منتصف إجراءات طلاق
and there was trouble about the compensation.
وكانت هناك مشكلة حيال التعويض
But that wouldn't matter if he died--
لكنّ ذلك لن يهم إذا مات
she'd get his inheritance instead!
فستحصل هي على إرثه
What are you talking about?!
!ما الذي تتكلم عنه؟
I heard my husband constantly refused your requests for a loan
سمعتُ أنّ زوجي رفض طلباتك المستمرة بالإقراض
because your company was on the verge of going out of business!
!لأنّ شركتك كانت على حافة الإقفال
So you couldn't handle it and killed him!
!لذا انفعلتَ وقمت بقتله
What?!
!مـ-مستحيل
Now, now. Calm down, ma'am.
اهدئي قليلاً يا سيّدة
By the way, Apartment Manager.
بالمناسبة يا مشرف المبنى
Is that main door the only way in and out of this building?
أذاك الباب الأمامي هو المدخل والمخرج الوحيد للمبنى؟
Yes.
أ-أجل، صحيح
And the only ones who entered besides the victim...
...والوحيدون الذي دخلوا اليوم إلى جانب الضحيّة
...were his wife, Dobashi-san, and Terasawa-san.
هم زوجته ودوباشي-سان وتيراساوا-سان فحسب
Moreover, each of you had a decent enough motive to kill the victim.
كما كان لكلّ منكم دافع قويّ لقتل الضحية
In other words, one of you three murdered him.
أي أنّ المجرم بينكم الثلاثة
You can't be serious!
!لا-لا يُعقل
First you, ma'am.
سنبدأ بك يا سيّدة
Please explain the situation when you found the body.
وضّحي لنا الظروف عندما عثرتِ على الجثّة رجاءً
It was a little after 5:00 when I arrived here.
أتيتُ لهذا المبنى بعد الخامسة بقليل
More precisely, it was just after 5:05.
كانت بعد الـ5:05 بقليل تحديداً
I record when everyone enters or leaves the building.
فأنا أسجّل دخول وخروج الجميع من المبنى
That'll be very handy for us!
سيفيدنا ذلك كثيراً
Please continue.
أكملي من فضلك
The reason I came here today
سبب قدومي اليوم
was to discuss the compensation with my husband one more time,
هو لمناقشة التعويض مع زوجي مُجدداً
just as Dobashi-san mentioned earlier.
كما ذكر دوباشي-سان
He and I have been living apart for quite a while now.
كنّا نعيش منفصلين لفترة
When I came in,
عندما دخلت
my husband was practicing Tai Chi on the veranda by himself.
كان يمارس زوجي التاي تشي على الشرفة بمفرده
Tai Chi?
التاي تشي؟
Yes.
أجل
My husband did it every morning and evening for his health.
كان يمارسه زوجي صباح ومساء كلّ يوم لصحّته
He didn't notice when I entered the room,
لم يلاحظني عندما دخلت
and I didn't call out to him.
ولم أناد عليه
When I looked out the veranda again after using the bathroom...
...عندما نظرتُ للشرفة مجدداً بعد استعمال الحمّام
...my husband was dead!
!وجدته ميتاً
So basically, your husband died while you were in the bathroom?
أي قُتل زوجك بينما كنتِ في الحمّام؟
Yes.
أجل
Pardon my asking, but how long were you in the bathroom for?
اعذريني، لكن كم قضيتِ في الحمّام بالضبط؟
Only about two minutes, I think...
قرابة دقيقتين فحسب وفقما أظن
Which means your husband died at approximately 5:08.
ما يعني أنّ زوجك مات عند 5:08 تقريباً
While you were in the bathroom,
بينما كنتِ في الحمّام
did you hear any sounds or people talking?
أسمعتِ أصوات أو كلام أحد؟
No.
كلا
Say, when you entered the apartment,
أخبريني يا عمّة، عندما دخلتِ الشقّة
were there any shoes by the door?
أكانت هناك أحذية عند الباب؟
Yes, just a pair of my husband's shoes.
أجل، حذاء زوجي فحسب
Thank you.
فهمت
Now you, Dobashi-san.
التالي، دوباشي-سان
Around what time did you first arrive?
متى أتيت لهذا المبنى بالضبط؟
A little before 5:00, I believe.
قُبيل الخامسة كما أظن
I was to meet with Imoto-kun at 5 o'clock, you see.
كان يُفترض أن ألتقي بإيموتو-كن عند الخامسة
More precisely, 4:58.
عند 4:58 بالتحديد
Just as his wife said, the reason I came here
كما قالت زوجته، سبب قدومي هنا
was to ask for a loan one last time.
هو طلب قرض منه لمرّة أخيرة
But...
...لكن
It's pointless, no matter how hard you try!
لا جدوى مهما طلبت
I have no desire or reason to help you out!
فلا رغبة ولا دافع لي لمساعدتك
Now please leave.
ارحل من فضلك
After that, I went to the roof.
ذهبتُ للسطح بعدها
To commit suicide.
لارتكاب الانتحار
Suicide?!
!الانتحار؟
But I couldn't do it.
لكنّي لم أستطع
I stood there for a while, in a daze.
وقفتُ هناك لفترة شارد الذهن
It was then that I heard her scream from the other side of the roof!
عندها سمعت صرخة الزوجة من الجانب الآخر للسطح
Then, when I rushed into the room...
بعدها أسرعتُ للغرفة
...Imoto-san was dead on the veranda, correct?
ووجدت إيموتو-سان ميتاً على الشرفة؟
Yes.
أجل
How about you, Terasawa-san?
ماذا عنك يا تيراساوا-سان؟
What do I have to do with it? I wasn't in the building.
لا علاقة لي، فقد كنتُ خارج المبنى
We just need to make sure.
علينا التحقق
Around what time did you leave the building?
متى غادرت المبنى بالضبط؟
I believe it was a little before 5:00...
...قبل الخامسة بقليل كما أذكر
4:50, to be precise.
عند 4:50 بالتحديد
And he didn't return until just after 5:12.
ولم يرجع حتّى بعد 5:12
But...
...لكن
"But"?
لكن؟
He came back from his golf practice rather earlier than usual...
...رجع من تمرين الغولف أبكر من المعتاد
I changed my mind on the way there.
غيّرتُ رأيي في طريقي فحسب
I've always been a bit spur-of-the-moment!
!لطالما كنتُ سريع التقلّب
What do you think, Mori-kun?
ما رأيك يا موري-كن؟
First, Terasawa-san.
بدايةً، تيراساوا-سان
You weren't in the building when Imoto-san was killed,
لم تكن في المبنى عندما قُتل إيموتو-سان
so you're not the killer.
لذا لستَ القاتل
The issue here is with his wife and Dobashi-san.
موضوعنا مع الزوجة ودوباشي-سان
First you, ma'am!
أنت أوّلاً يا سيّدة
You said you found your husband's body after you left the bathroom,
قلتِ أنّك وجدت جثّة زوجك بعد مغادرتك الحمّام
but there's the possibility that you never went to the bathroom,
لكن هناك احتمال بعدم ذهابك للحمّام أصلاً
and that you killed your husband, pretended to find him,
وقتلك زوجك، ثم تظاهرك بالعثور على جثّته
and then screamed!
والصراخ
What?!
!مـ-ماذا؟
And you, Dobashi-san!
وأنت يا دوباشي-سان
You said you went up to the roof
قلتَ أنك صعدت للسطح
after Imoto-san refused to lend you money,
بعدما رفض إيموتو-سان إقراضك
but there's a possibility you were actually in his office
لكن هناك احتمال أنّك كنت في مكتبه
or with him on the veranda!
!أو معه في الشرفة
All you can see from here is a small part of the veranda.
ما يمكن رؤيته من هنا هو جزء صغير من الشرفة فحسب
It's also possible that when his wife came in,
هناك احتمال أنّك كنت في الشرفة
you were on the veranda or in his office,
أو في المكتب عندما دخلت الزوجة
killed the victim while she was in the bathroom,
وقتلت الضحيّة بينما كانت هي في الحمّام
and then went up to the roof.
ثم صعدت للسطح
You got it all wrong!
!كـ-كلا
I was already on the roof by the time she came in here!
!كنتُ على السطح بوقت وصولها هنا
She even said that only Imoto-kun's shoes were by the door!
قالت بنفسها أنّ حذاء إيموتو-كن !وحده كان عند الباب
It's also possible that she didn't remember correctly!
يُحتمل أنّها لم تتذكر بدقّة
Or do you have proof that you were on the roof the whole time?!
أم تملك دليلاً بوجودك على السطح طوال الوقت؟
Proof?
دليل؟
No, there was no one on the roof, so...
كلا، لم يكن هناك أحد على السطح
That's right! I heard a sound!
!صحيح! سمعتُ صوتاً
A sound?!
صوت؟
Yes. It was a loud, metallic sound.
أجل، كان صوتاً معدنياً مرتفعاً
It came from the area around this veranda.
أتى من اتّجاه هذه الشرفة
You heard a sound?
سمعت صوتاً؟
Yes. A metallic one.
أجل، وقعه معدنيّ
Hey, could that sound have been something hitting the handrail?
أيمكن أنّه كان صوت شيء أصاب السور المعدنيّ؟
See, there's a fresh mark on it!
انظروا، هناك آثر جديد عليه
It appears something hit it from below...
...يبدو أنّ شيئاً صلباً أصابه من الأسفل
That's it! That's the sound!
!هذا! هذا هو الصوت
The marks look similar...
الأثر مشابه
But the other mark was made coming up...
لكن الأثر الآخر كان من الأسفل
Yes.
أجل
But there's no question that someone hit it.
لكن لا شكّ أن أحداً طرقه
Did you hear the sound, ma'am?
أسمعتِ الصوت يا سيّدتي؟
No.
كلا
I probably didn't hear it because I was in the bathroom.
لم أسمع لأنّي كنت في الحمام غالباً
That's odd...
غريب
Why would someone put a mark in a place like that?
لمَ قد يتسبب أحد بأثر في موضع كذاك؟
It makes no sense...
غير منطقيّ
This handrail seems suspicious,
يبدو هذا السور مثيراً للريبة
but in my opinion none of them seem to be lying, either.
لكن لا يظهر لي أنّ أحد الاثنين كاذب أيضاً
But Inspector!
!لكن حضرة المفتّش
Just because Dobashi heard a sound from the handrail
سماع دوباشي لصوت طرق السور
that isn't proof that he was on the roof!
!ليس دليلاً على كونه في السطح
He or the victim might've made the sound
ربما تسبب هو أو الضحية بالصوت
while he was on the veranda!
!بينما كان في الشرفة
Besides, if the killer was someone else,
وأيضاً لو كان القاتل شخصاً آخر
that means they flew in like a bird to kill the victim,
هذا يعني أنّه طار كالطير وقتل الضحيّة
then flew off the exact same way they came!
!ثم طار مجدداً كما أتى
Which would never, ever happen!
!ذلك مستحيل
You do have a point...
...مـ-معك حق
A bird? A bird?!
طير؟ طير... طير؟
Come to think of it, the spot where the bird fell--
...بالمناسبة، المكان الذي سقط فيه ذاك الطير
--was over there!
!كان ذاك
Directly in front of the mark on this handrail!
!أمام الأثر على السور تماماً
The location where the victim collapsed...
...موضع سقوط الضحيّة
The location where the bird fell...
...موضع سقوط الطير
The mark on the handrail!
...الأثر على السور
An abandoned building across the street?
بناء مهجور مقابل الشرفة؟
Now I see!
فهمت الآن
This is the killer's trick!
!هذه حيلة القاتل
The murder weapon wasn't a flower pot!
!لم يكن سلاح الجريمة أصيص أزهار
The killer was that person!
!القاتل هو ذاك الشخص
My deductions can't possibly be wrong.
لا يمكن أنّ استنتاجي خاطئ
She's his wife, who lives separately from him.
إنّها زوجته وتعيش منفصلة عنه
He's the president of an import company.
إنّه رئيس شركة استيراد
And he's the former owner of a fishing goods store.
وهو مالك سابق لمتجر معدّات صيد
Which means the killer is...
...ما يعني أنّ القاتل
Say, Inspector.
إذاً حضرة المفتش
I'll be returning to my apartment now...
سأرجع لشقّتي الآن
Oh, right.
حسناً
You can go for today...
يمكنك الانصراف لليوم
I can't let that happen!
!لا يمكنني ترك ذلك يحدث
I have to make the old man realize it somehow!
!عليّ لفت انتباه العمّ للأمر بشكلٍ ما
Found it!
!ها هو
Have you figured anything out, Mori-kun?
هل اكتشفت شيئاً يا موري-كن؟
No, nothing at all...
كلا... لا شيء
And this is the mark on the handrail.
وهنا... الأثر على السور
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل يا عمّ؟
Conan, that bird fell down there, right?
كونان، سقط ذاك الطير هناك، صحيح؟
Yeah, that's right!
!أجل، صحيح
That's it!
!فهمت
The victim, the mark, that bird, and that abandoned building!
،الضحيّة والأثر على السور والطير كما ذاك المبنى المهجور
They're all directly lined up!
!كلّها على خطّ واحد
I know who did it, Inspector!
!عرفتُ الفاعل حضرة المفتّش
Really? Who?!
حقّاً؟! من إذاً؟
Don't get too ahead of yourself.
لا تستعجل
I'll explain everything atop that abandoned building!
سأوضّح كلّ شيء على ذاك المبنى المهجور
Come again?
ماذا؟
Come on, Mori-kun.
موري-كن
What are you checking for in a place like this?
ما الذي تتفقده في مكان كهذا؟
I don't see what this has to do with the murder...
لا أرى علاقة له بالجريمة
Everyone gather around here, please!
اجتمعوا هنا من فضلكم
First, allow me to ask.
دعوني أسأل بدايةً
Ma'am, Dobashi-san, Terasawa-san...
سيّدتي، دوباشي-سان، تيراساوا-سان
Have any of you ever been here before?
أسبق لأحدكم القدوم هنا قبلاً؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا
Me neither.
ولا أنا
Nor have I.
كذلك أنا
Then allow me to explain.
دعوني أشرح إذاً
You can see the victim's veranda from here, can't you?
يمكنكم رؤية شرفة الضحيّة من هنا، صحيح؟
Yes, but what does that have to do with anything?
أجل، لكن ما أهميّة ذلك؟
Have you ever heard of surf casting, Inspector?
أسبق وسمعت بصيد الضفّة حضرة المفتش؟
Surf casting?
صيد الضفّة؟
It's a type of fishing that uses a so-called "spinning reel"
إنّه نوع من الصيد تستعمل فيه ما تُدعى بالبكرة الدورانية
to allow the fisher to cast the line some dozens of meters out.
كي يستطيع الصيّاد رمي الخيط مسافة عشرات الأمتار
The killer used this technique from here
استعمل القاتل هذه التقنية من هنا
to hit the victim's head with a weight as he stood on the veranda!
وأصاب رأس الضحيّة بثقلٍ !وهو على الشرفة هناك
What?!
!ماذا؟
This footprint is the proof.
الدليل هو آثار الأقدام هذه
The left foot is in front and with a lot of weight on it.
أثر القدم اليسرى محفور ويتقدم اليمنى
This was made when the killer flung the pole in an overhand fashion.
تركه القاتل عندما كان يهمّ بقذف القصبة فوق رأسه
Like this!
هكذا
When he was killed, the victim was performing Tai Chi,
عندما قُتل، كان الضحيّة يمارس التاي تشي
which is known for its slow movements.
المعروفة بحركاتها البطيئة
Using this fact,
استغلّ القاتل ذلك
the killer swung the fishing pole when he turned away!
وقذف الثقل عندما أدار الضحيّة ظهره
And as it was reeled in--
...وبينما كان يُسحب
--the weight hit the handrail.
أصاب الثقل السور المعدنيّ
So that's the sound I heard?
ذاك كان الصوت الذي سمعتُه إذاً؟
Correct.
أجل
The killer didn't realize the weight had left a mark when it happened.
لم يدرك القاتل أنّ الثقل ترك أثراً آنذاك
And there was one other miscalculation on the killer's part.
كما كان هناك خطأ آخر في حساباته
As the weight was being reeled in, it hit a bird in mid-air.
أصاب الثقل طيراً في طريقه بينما يسحبه
The bird you picked up had probably received a concussion.
كان الطير الذي حملتَه قد أُصيب بارتجاج دماغيّ غالباً
But Mori-kun, it's over thirty meters to that veranda.
لكن يا موري-كن، المسافة تُقارب 30 متراً للشرفة
Could someone really cast a weight that far with such precision?
أيمكن لشخص قذف وزن لتلك المسافة بدقّة حقاً؟
With enough practice, yes.
يمكنه بالتمرين
Especially for someone who's good at surf casting.
لا سيّما بالنسبة لشخص يجيد صيد الضفّة بالتحديد
Isn't that right, Terasawa-san?
أليس كذلك يا تيراساوا-سان؟
Terasawa-san.
تيراساوا-سان
Those shoes you're wearing right now
الحذاء الذي ترتديه الآن
should undoubtedly match these footprints.
يُفترض أن يُطابق آثار الأقدام هنا بلا شك
And if we look hard enough around this abandoned building,
كما لو فتّشنا هذا المبنى المهجور بعناية
we'll probably--
...سنجد غالباً
Hey! There's something on the ground here!
!يا عمّ! يوجد شيء على الأرض هنا
What's that?
ما هذا؟
I know what this is! It's a pole grip!
!أعرفه! إنّها قبضة قصبة
A pole grip?
قبضة قصبة؟
Yeah!
أجل
Sometimes after fishermen connect fishing rods together,
بعدما يربط الصيّادون قصبات الصيد أحياناً
they won't come undone.
يصعب فكّها
So to prevent their hands from slipping,
لذا لمنع أيديهم من الانزلاق
they place rubber tubes or rubber bands near where the rods connect,
يضعون أنابيب أو شرائط مطاطية عند مربط القصبات
and then pull the rods apart while twisting them in opposite directions!
ثمّ ينزعون القصبات بلفّها في الاتّجاه المعاكس
You're pretty smart to know that...
...من المُبهر أنّك تعرف ذلك
I just happened to see it on a TV fishing show yesterday.
صادف أن رأيتُه في برنامج صيد على التلفاز بالأمس
Come to think of it, they had their gloves off when they used these.
بالمناسبة، كانوا يخلعون قفّازات أيديهم عندما يستعملون هذه
Because they would slip!
لأنّها ستنزلق
Which means the killer's fingerprints should be on it!
!ما يعني أنّ بصمات الفاعل ستكون عليها
Terasawa-san. Your fingerprints!
تيراساوا-سان، بصماتك أنت
I can't help but laugh.
لا يسعني سوى الضّحك
He took over my store
استولى على متجري
and said he was going to build a fashion building in its place!
وقال أنّه سيبني مبنى أزياء حديث مكانه
I said I'd give up ownership if he'd just spare the store, but...
أخبرته أنّي سأترك الملكية له ...إذا أبقى المتجر على الأقل، لكنه
There's no point in keeping this dinky store around.
لا جدوى من إبقاء متجر تافه كهذا
What's so fun about catching fish, anyway?
ما المسلّي في صيد السمك أصلاً؟
What a joke!
يا للسخافة
What do you losers see in it at all?
ما الذي يعجب الفاشلون بهذا؟
My precious fishing rod!
قصبة صيدي الغالية
He destroyed it before my very eyes!
!حطّمها أمامي
I absolutely couldn't let him get away with it!
!لم أستطع تركه يفلت بفعلته
Cases like that are a piece of cake for me!
!قضايا كتلك أشبه بالماء لي
Did he actually make that fishing rod toy
هل صنع لعبة قصبة الصيد تلك
to make me realize it?!
كي يلفت انتباهي في الواقع؟
I got something!
!أمسكتُ بشيء
Dad!
!أبي
Old man!
!يا عمّ
Who am I kidding?
...مستحيل
Get back here, Shinichi!
!ارجع بسرعة يا شينتشي
I finally found you!
!وجدتكم أخيراً
Let me go before the bomber gets away!
!دعني! علينا الإسراع وإلّا سيفلت الفاعل
Ah! So that's how it was!
!فهمت! هكذا إذاً
In the eyes of the killer, this was an unexpected murder!
!كانت هذه جريمة غير متوقّعة بالنسبة للقاتل
The Game Company Murder Case
جريمة قتل شركة الألعاب
On the next Conan:
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Cloakroom Tag.
بطاقة حجرة إيداع
Next episode the men in black make an appearance.
!يظهرٌ رجل برداء أسود في الحلقة القادمة
Conan, I'll return to my adult form, too.
كونان، سأرجع لكوني بالغاً أيضاً